Painting Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Painting United States (Box 148)
  - Known Artists (Box 150)
    - WILLIAMS, William, 1727-1791 (Box 187)
    - WIMAR, Charles Ferdinand, 1828-1862 (Box 187)
    - WINTER, Charles, 1869- (Box 187)
    - WINTER, Ezra A., 1886-1949 (Box 187)
    - WOLCUTT, William (Box 187)
    - WOLLASTON, John, 1736-1775 (Box 187)
      - New York (Box 187)
    - WOOD, George B. (Box 187)
    - WOOD, Grant, 1891-1942 (Box 187)
    - WOOD, Thomas W., 1823-1903 (Box 187)
    - WOODSIDE, John A., fl. 1817-1850 (Box 187)
    - WOODVILLE, Richard Caton, 1825-1855 (Box 187)
    - WRIGHT, Joseph, 1756-1793 (Box 187)
    - WRIGHT, Joseph, 1756-1793 (Box 187)
    - WYETH, Andrew Newell, 1917- (Box 187)
    - XCERON, Jean, 1890- (Box 187)
    - ZAYAS, Marius da (Box 187)
    - ZERBE, Karl (Box 187)
    - ZOGBAUM, Rufus F., 1849-1925 (Box 187)
    - ZORACH, Margarite, 1888- (Box 187)
    - ZORACH, William (Box 187)
    - ZOX, Larry, 1936 (Box 187)
- Painting Latin America (Box 188)
  - Painting Argentina (Box 188)
  - Painting Bolivia (Box 188)
  - Painting Brazil (Box 188)
    - PORTINARI, Candido, 1903- (Box 188)
  - Painting Chile (Box 188)
    - MATIA ECHAUBREN, Roberto, 1911- (Box 188)
  - Painting Colombia (Box 189)
  - Painting Ecuador (Box 189)
  - Painting Guatemala (Box 189)
  - Painting Mexico (Box 189)
    - 16th century (Box 189)
    - 17th century (Box 189)
    - 18th century (Box 189)
    - 19th century (Box 189–190)
    - ALCIBAR, Don Jose de (Box 190)
    - ATL, Dr, 1875-1964) (Box 190)
    - BARREDA, Ignacio Maria (Box 190)
    - BRACHO, Angel (Box 190)
    - BUSTO, Hermenegildo, 1832-1907 (Box 190)
    - CABRERA, Miguel, 1695-1768 (Box 190)
    - CASTELLANOS, Julio, 1905- (Box 190)
    - CHARROT, Jean, 1898- (Box 190)
    - CLAVE, Pelagrina (Box 190)
    - CORDERO, Juan, 1822-1884 (Box 190)
    - GOITIA, Francisco, 1884- (Box 190)
    - GONZALEZ, Carmarena Jorge (Box 190)
    - GUERRERO, Galvan Jesus, 1910- (Box 190)
    - HERRAN, Saturnino (Box 190)
    - KAHLO, Frida, 1907-1954 (Box 190)
    - MALS, Miguel Jose (Box 190)
    - MORADO, Chavez, 20th century (Box 190)
    - O' GORMAN, Juan, 1905-1982 (Box 190)
    - OROZCO, Jose Clemente, 18823-1949 (Box 190–191)
      - Buenos Aires (Box 191)
      - Claremont (Box 191)
      - Guadalajara (Box 191)
      - Hanover, NH (Box 191)
      - Jiquilpan (Box 191)
      - Mexico City (Box 191)
        - National Preparatory School (Box 191)
        - Normal School (Box 191)
        - Supreme Court of Justice (Box 191)
      - New York (Box 191)
    - PACHEO, Maximo, 1907- (Box 192)
    - PAROVANI, Jose (Box 192)
    - RIVERA, Diego, 1886-1957 (Box 192)
      - Chapingo (Box 192)
      - Cuernavaca (Box 192)
      - Detroit (Box 192)
      - Mexico City (Box 192)
        - Lerma Waterworks (Box 192)
        - Ministry of Education (Box 192)
        - National Palace (Box 192)
        - National Preparatory School (Box 192)
        - Prado Hotel (Box 192)
      - San Franciso (Box 192)
    - SEQUEIROS (Box 192)
      - Chapultapec (Box 192–193)
      - Chillan (Box 193)
      - Mexico City (Box 193)
      - New York (Box 193)
      - Princeton (Box 193)
    - TAMAYO, Rufino, 1900- (Box 193)
    - URUETA, Cordelia (Box 193)
    - VELASCO, Jose Maria, 1840-1912 (Box 193)
    - VILLAPANDO, Cristobal de, 1652-1714 (Box 193)
  - Painting Peru (Box 193–194)
    - SABOGAL, Jose, 1888-1956 (Box 194)
  - Painting Uruguay (Box 194)
    - BLANES, Juan Manuel (Box 194)
  - Painting Venezuela (Box 194–195)
  - Painting Caribbean (Box 195)
  - Painting Cuba (Box 195)
    - PELAEZ de Casal Amelia, 1897- (Box 195)
    - LAM, Wilfredo, 1902-1982 (Box 195)
    - BERMUDEZ, Cundo, 1914- (Box 195)
  - Painting Haiti (Box 195)
- Painting Spain (Box 195)
  - 12th Century (Box 195)
    - Various Titles (Box 195)
  - 14th Century (Box 195)
    - Various Titles (Box 195)
  - 15th Century (Box 195)
    - Various Titles (Box 195)
  - 16th Century (Box 195)
    - Various Titles (Box 195)
  - 17th Century (Box 195)
    - Various Titles (Box 195)
  - 18th Century (Box 195)
    - Various Titles (Box 195)
  - 20th Century (Box 195)
    - Various Titles (Box 195)
    - Bassa, Ferrer, ac.1324-1349 (Box 195)
    - Bayeu, Francisco, 1734-1795 (Box 195)
    - Berruguette, Alonso, 1480-1561 (Box 195)
    - Berruguette, Pedro, ac.1477-1503 (Box 195)
    - Borrossa, Luis, ac.1390-1424 (Box 195)
    - Cano, Alonso, 1601-1667 (Box 195)
    - Carreno de Miranda, Juan, 1614-1685 (Box 195)
    - Casas, Ramon, 1866-1932 (Box 195)
    - Coello, Claudio, 1642-1693 (Box 195)
    - Correa, Marcos (Box 196)
    - Dali, Salvador, 1904-1988 (Box 196–197)
    - Dalmau, Luis (Box 197)
    - Fernandez, Alejo, c.1470-1543 (Box 197)
    - Ferrer, Jaume (Box 197)
    - Gallegos, Fernando, (school of) (Box 197)
    - Goya, Francisco Jose de, 1746-1828 (Box 197)
      - Drawings (Box 197)
      - Paintings (Box 197)
        - Various Titles (Box 197)
        - Madrid (Box 197)
          - Various Titles (Box 197)
          - Academia de San Fernando (Box 197)
          - Prado (Box 198)
            - Various Titles (Box 198)
            - Fantastic Vision (Box 198)
            - Insurrection of May (Box 198)
            - Majas (Box 198)
            - Portraits (Box 198)
            - Shooting in Madrid (Box 198)
            - Tapestry Cartoons (Box 198)
            - S. Antonio de La Florida (Box 198)
          - New York (Box 198)
            - Frick Collection (Box 198)
            - Metropolitan (Box 198)
          - Northampton (Box 198)
          - Paris (Box 198)
          - San Diego (Box 198)
          - Washington (Box 198)
    - El Greco, 1541-1614 (Box 198)
      - Various Titles (Box 198)
      - Barcelona (Box 198)
      - Boston (Box 199)
      - Budapest (Box 199)
      - Cambridge (Box 199)
      - Chicago (Box 199)
      - Cincinnati (Box 199)
      - Cleveland (Box 199)
      - Edinburgh (Box 199)
      - Florence (Box 199)
      - Glasgow (Box 199)
      - Havana (Box 199)
      - London (Box 199)
      - Madrid (Box 199)
        - Various Titles (Box 199)
        - Escorial (Box 199)
      - M inneapolis (Box 199)
      - Munich (Box 199)
      - New York (Box 199)
        - Frick Collection (Box 199)
        - Metropolitan (Box 199)
      - Philadelphia (Box 199)
      - Rochester (Box 199)
      - San Francisco (Box 199)
      - Toledo, Spain (Box 199)
        - Museo (Casa) del Greco (Box 199)
        - S. Tome (Box 199)
        - Museum S. Vincente (Box 199)
      - Villanueva (Box 200)
      - Washington (Box 200)
    - Gris, Juan, 1887-1927 (Box 200)
    - Herrera, Francisco, elder, 1576-1656 (Box 200)
    - Homar, Gaspar, 1870-1953 (Box 200)
    - Huguet, Jaime (Box 200)
    - Jimeno y Planes, Rafael, 1761-1825 (Box 200)
    - Juan de Flandes, ac.1496-1519 (Box 200)
    - Joanes, Juan de, 1500-1579 (Box 200)
    - Lopez, Vicente, 1772-1850 (Box 200)
    - Lucas, Eugenio, 1824-1870 (Box 200)
    - Melendez, Luis, 1716-1780 (Box 200)
    - Miro, Joan, 1893-1983 (Box 200)
      - New Haven (Box 200)
      - New York (Box 201)
      - Paris (Box 201)
    - Morales, Luis de, 1509-1586 (Box 201)
    - Murillo, Bartolome Esteban, 1618-1682 (Box 201)
      - Various (Box 201)
      - Chatsworth (Box 201)
      - Dresden (Box 201)
      - Leningrad (Box 201)
      - London (Box 201)
      - Madrid (Box 201)
        - Prado (Box 201)
      - Munich (Box 201)
      - Paris (Box 201)
      - Seville (Box 201)
        - Various (Box 201)
        - Provincial Museum (Box 201)
        - Washington (Box 201)
    - Pacheco, Francisco, 1571-1654 (Box 201)
    - Paret, Luis, 1746-1799 (Box 201)
    - Pereda, Antonio, 1608-1678 (Box 201)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973 (Box 201)
      - Photograph (Box 201)
      - Paintings (Box 201)
        - 1893-1899 (Box 201)
        - 1900-1902 (Box 202)
        - 1903 (Box 202)
        - 1904-1905 (Box 202)
        - 1906-1907 (Box 202)
        - 1908-1909 (Box 202)
        - 1910-1911 (Box 202)
        - 1912-1918 (Box 202)
        - 1919-1923 (Box 202–203)
        - 1924-1928 (Box 203)
        - 1929-1936 (Box 203)
        - 1937 (Box 203)
        - 1938-1939 (Box 203)
        - 1940-1949 (Box 203–204)
        - 1950 (Box 204)
    - Ribalta, Francisco de, 1551-1628 (Box 204)
    - Ribera, Jusepe, 1588-1652 (Box 204)
      - Various (Box 204)
      - Madrid (Box 204)
      - Naples (Box 204)
      - New Haven (Box 204)
      - New York (Box 204)
      - Paris (Box 204)
      - Rome (Box 204)
      - Vienna (Box 204)
    - Serra, Brothers (Box 204)
    - Sorolla y Bastida, Joaquin, 1863-1923 (Box 204)
    - Tapies, Antonio, 1923- (Box 205)
    - Tristan de Escamilla, Luis, 1586-1624 (Box 205)
    - Valdes-Leal, Juan de, 1622-1690 (Box 205)
    - Vargas, Luis de, 1502-1568 (Box 205)
    - Velazquez, Diego, 1599-1660 (Box 205)
      - Various Titles (Box 205)
      - Berlin (Box 205)
      - Boston (Box 205)
      - Cambridge (Box 205)
      - Dresden (Box 205)
      - Florence (Box 205)
      - London (Box 205)
      - Madrid (Box 205)
        - Prado (Box 205)
          - Various Titles (Box 205)
          - Adoration of Magi (Box 205)
          - Coronation of the Virgin (Box 205)
          - Drinkers (Box 205)
          - Forge of Vulcan (Box 205)
          - Las Meninas (Box 206)
          - Mars (Box 206)
          - Surrender of Breda (Box 206)
          - Tapestry Weavers (Spinners) (Box 206)
          - Portraits (Box 206)
            - Various Titles (Box 206)
            - Aesop (Box 206)
            - Balthazar Carlos (Box 206)
            - Boy of Vallecas (Box 206)
            - Buffon of Philip IV (Box 206)
            - Duke of Olivares (Box 206)
            - Fernando of Austria (Box 206)
            - Idiot of Corias (Box 206)
            - Infanta Maria Teresa (Box 206)
            - Isabel of Bourbon (Box 206)
            - Maria Anna of Austria (Box 206)
            - Philiph IV (Box 206)
            - Dwarfs (Box 206)
      - Naples (Box 207)
      - New York (Box 207)
      - Paris (Box 207)
      - Rome (Box 207)
      - Vienna (Box 207)
      - Washington (Box 207)
    - Vergos, Pablo, d.1495- (Box 207)
    - Vermejo, Bartolomeo (Box 207)
    - Villegas y Cordero, 1848-1921 (Box 207)
    - Vines, Hernando, 1904 (Box 207)
    - Zuluoga, Ignacio, 1870-1945 (Box 207)
    - Zurburan, Francisco de, 1598-1664 (Box 207)
      - Various Titles (Box 207)
      - Guadalupe (Box 207)
      - Madrid (Box 208)
        - Various Titles (Box 208)
        - Prado (Box 208)
      - Munich (Box 208)
      - New York (Box 208)
      - Paris (Box 208)
      - Philadelphia (Box 208)
      - Seville (Box 208)
- Painting Sweden (Box 208)
  - Carlsund, Otto G., 1897-1948 (Box 208)
- Painting Switzerland (Box 208)
  - Various (Box 208)
  - Erni, Hans, 1909- (Box 208)
  - Giacometti, Alberto, 1901-1965 (Box 208)
  - Hodler, Ferdinand, 1853-1918 (Box 208)
  - Klee, Paul, 1879-1940 (Box 209)
  - Liotard, Jean Etienne, 1702-1789 (Box 209)
  - Schneider, Gerard, 1896 (Box 209)
- Painting Italy (Box 209)
  General
  For materials transferred to the Yale University Art Gallery, see list following this section (pp. 155-163)
  - 15th century (Box 210)
    - Drawing (Box 210)
    - Painting (Box 210)
    - CASSONI (Box 210)
    - FLORENTINE School (Box 210)
    - SIENESE School (Box 210)
    - UMBRIAN School (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Fucecchio, Tuscan School (Box 211)
    - MASTER of Staffolo, fl. Ca. 1420-1450 (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Apollo and Daphne Legend (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Castello Nativity (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Chiostoro degli Aranca (Box 211)
    - MASTER of 1419 (Box 211)
    - MASTER of Monte Oliveto (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Bambino Vispo (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Barberini Panels (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Griges Crucifixion (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Jarves Cassoni (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Judgment of Paris (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Lanckowski Annunciation (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the Osservanza Altar (Box 211)
    - PRATO Master (Box 211)
    - MASTER of Pratovecchio (Box 211)
    - QUARRATA Master (Box 211)
    - MASTER of the S. Croce Tournament (Box 211)
    - FAKES (Box 211)
  - 16th century (Box 211–212)
    - MASTER of Santo Spirito (Box 212)
    - MASTER of the Griggs Tondo (Box 212)
    - MASTER of the Kress Landscapes, fl. ca. 1505-1530 (Box 212)
  - 17th century (Box 212)
  - 18th century (Box 212)
  - Known Artists (Box 212)
    - ABBATE, Nicolo dell', 1512-1571 (Box 212)
    - AGNOLO degli Erri, ca. 1450-1500 (Box 212)
    - AGOSTINO da Lodi (Box 212)
    - ALAMAGNA, Giovanni de ("da Murano"), d. 1450 (Box 212)
    - ALBANI, Francesco, 1578-1660 (Box 212)
    - ALBERTINELLI, Mariottto, 1474-1515 (Box 212)
    - ALESSO di Andrea (Box 212)
    - ALLORI, Allessandro, 1535-1607 (Box 212)
    - ALLORI, Cristoforo (Box 212)
    - ALTISSIMO, Cristofano, 1550-1605 (Box 212)
    - ALUNNO di Benozzo (Box 213)
    - AMADEI, Giuliano,. 1446-d. 1496 (Box 213)
    - AMBROGIO di Baldese (pseudo), SEE PSEUDO-AMBROGIO… (Box 213)
    - ANDREA da Bologna (Box 213)
    - ANDREA da Firenze, fl. 1346-d. 1379 (Box 213)
      - Florence (Box 213)
        - S. Maria Novella Spanish Chapel (Box 213)
        - Church Militant (Box 213)
          - Church Militant Details (Box 213)
          - Crucifixion (Box 213)
      - Pisa (Box 213)
    - ANDREA di Giusto, fl. 1424-1498 (Box 213)
    - ANDREA di Niccolo di Giacomo (Box 213)
    - ANGELICO, Fra Giovanni da Fiesole, 1387-1455 (Box 213–215)
      - Berlin (Box 213–215)
      - Boston (Box 213–215)
        - Gardner Museum (Box 213–215)
        - Museum of Fine Arts (Box 213–215)
      - Cambridge, MA (Box 213–215)
        - Fogg Museum (Box 213–215)
      - Cortona (Box 213–215)
      - Detroit (Box 213–215)
      - Dublin (Box 213–215)
      - Florence (Box 213–215)
        - S. Marco Museum (Box 213–215)
          - I. Frescoes (Box 213–215)
            - Annunciation (Box 213–215)
            - Christ Mocked (Box 213–215)
            - Coronation of the Virgin (Box 213–215)
            - Crucifixion (Box 213–215)
            - Crucifixion with S. Domenico (Box 213–215)
            - Institution of the Eucharist (Box 213–215)
            - Transfiguration (Box 213–215)
          - II. Panel Paintings (Box 213–215)
            - Annalena Madonna (Box 213–215)
            - Annunciation and Adoration (Box 213–215)
            - Coronation of the Virgin (Box 213–215)
            - Last Judgment (Box 213–215)
            - Linaiuou Triptych (Box 213–215)
            - S. Marco Altarpiece (Box 213–215)
          - Silver Chest Panels (Box 213–215)
      - Franfurt (Box 213–215)
      - London (Box 213–215)
      - Madrid (Box 213–215)
      - Munich (Box 213–215)
      - New York (Box 213–215)
      - Orvieto (Box 213–215)
      - Paris (Box 213–215)
        - Louvre (Box 213–215)
      - Perugia (Box 213–215)
      - Rome (Box 213–215)
        - Vatican-Chapel of Nicolas V (Box 213–215)
      - Washington (Box 213–215)
    - ANSALDO, Giovanni Andrea, 1584-1638 (Box 215)
    - ANSUINO da Forli (Box 215)
    - ANTONELLO da Messina, ca.1430-1479 (Box 215)
    - Berlin (Box 215)
      - Dresden (Box 215)
      - London (Box 215)
      - New York (Box 215)
      - Palermo (Box 215)
      - Paris (Box 215)
      - Vienna (Box 215)
      - Washington (Box 215)
    - ANTONELLO da Saliba, ca. 1466-1535 (Box 215)
    - ATONIAZZO Romano, fl. 1461, d. ca. 1508 (Box 215)
      - Boston (Box 215)
      - Cambridge (Box 215)
      - Ravenna (Box 215)
      - Rome (Box 215)
    - ANTONIO da Negroponte (Box 215)
    - APOLLONIO di Giovanni (workshop of), ca. 1450-1500 (Box 215–216)
      - New Haven (Box 216)
        - Tournament in Piazza S. Croce (Box 216)
        - Dido and Aeneas (Box 216)
        - Meeting of Solomon and Sheba (Box 216)
    - APPIANI, Andrea, 1754-1817 (Box 216)
    - ARCANGELO di Cola, fl. 1416-1429 (Box 216)
    - ARCIMBOLDO, Giuseppe, ca. 1527-1593 (Box 216)
    - BACCHIACA, Francesco, 1494-1495 to 1557 (Box 216)
    - BACICCIO, il (Box 216)
    - BADILE, Giovanni Antonio, 1516-1617 to 1560 (Box 216)
    - BAGLIONE, Giovanni, ca.1566-1643 (Box 216)
    - BALDI, Lazzaro, 1624-1703 (Box 216)
    - BALDOVINETTI, Alesso, ca. 1425-1499 (Box 216)
      - Cleveland (Box 216)
      - Florence (Box 216)
        - SS. Annunziata (Box 216)
        - S. Egidio (Box 216)
        - S. Marco (Box 216)
        - Uffizi (Box 216)
      - London (Box 216)
      - Paris (Box 216)
        - Louvre (Box 216)
      - Washington (Box 216)
    - BALLA, Giacomo, ca. 1871-1958 (Box 216)
    - BANDINELLI, Bartolomeo, 1488-1560 (Box 217)
    - BARBARI, Jacopo de', ca. 1460-1516 (Box 217)
    - BARNA da Siena, fl. 1369-1380 (Box 217)
      - Boston (Box 217)
      - Cambridge (Box 217)
      - S. Gimignano (Box 217)
    - BAROCCI, Federico, 1528-1612 (Box 217)
      - Florence (Box 217)
      - Madrid (Box 217)
      - New York (Box 217)
      - Perugia (Box 217)
      - Rome (Box 217)
    - BARTOLO di Fredi, fl. 1353-d. 1410 (Box 217)
      - Siena (Box 217)
      - Washington (Box 217)
    - BARTOLOMMEO, Fra, 1472-1517 (Box 217–218)
      - Drawings (Box 218)
      - Paintings (Box 218)
        - Florence (Box 218)
          - Accademia (Box 218)
          - S. Marco Museum (Box 218)
          - Palazzo Pitti (Box 218)
        - London (Box 218)
        - Lucca (Box 218)
          - Cathedral (Box 218)
        - Paris (Box 218)
        - Richomond (Box 218)
        - Rome (Box 218)
    - BARTOLOMMEO di Giovanni (Box 218)
      - Paris (Box 218)
        - Feast of Nastagio degli Onesti (Box 218)
    - BASAITI, Marco, fl. 1407-d. 1521 (Box 218)
    - BASCHENIS, Evaristo, 16-7-1617 to 1677 (Box 218)
    - BASSANO, Jacopo da Ponte, 1510-1592 (Box 218)
      - Cleveland (Box 218)
      - Milan (Box 218)
      - Naples (Box 218)
      - Rome (Box 218)
      - Venice (Box 218)
      - Vienna (Box 218)
      - Washington (Box 218)
    - BASTIANI, Lazzaro, ca. 1430-1512 (Box 218)
    - BATONI, Pompeo Girolamo, 1702-1708 to 1787 (Box 218)
    - BATTAGLIOLI, Francesco, fl. 1750 (Box 218)
    - BECCAFUMI, Domenico di Pace, 1486-1551 (Box 218–219)
      - Siena (Box 219)
    - BELLA, S. della (Box 219)
    - BELLINI, Gentile, ca. 1429-1507 (Box 219–220)
      - Berlin (Box 220)
      - Boston (Box 220)
      - Chicago (Box 220)
      - London (Box 220)
      - Milan (Box 220)
      - New York (Box 220)
      - Venice (Box 220)
        - Accademia (Box 220)
    - BELLINI, Giovanni, ca. 1430-1516 (Box 220)
      - Drawings (Box 220)
      - Paintings (Box 220)
        - Berlin (Box 220)
        - Boston (Box 220)
        - Cambridge, MA (Box 220)
        - Florence (Box 220)
        - London (Box 220)
          - National Gallery (Box 220)
            - Agony in the Garden (Box 220)
            - Doge Leonardo Lerodario (Box 220)
            - Madonna and Child (Box 220)
        - Milan (Box 220)
        - Murano (Box 220)
        - Naples (Box 220)
        - New York (Box 220)
          - Bache Collection (Box 220)
          - Frick Collection (Box 220)
          - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 220)
        - Paris (Box 220)
        - Philadelphia (Box 220)
        - Venice (Box 220)
          - Accademia (Box 220)
            - Five Allegories Triumph of Venice (Box 220)
            - Giovanelli Madonna (Box 220)
            - Madonna di S. Giobbe (Box 220)
            - Madonna of the Trees (Box 220)
            - Madonna and SS. George and Paul (Box 220)
          - S. Maria dei Frari (Box 220)
          - S. Zaccaria (Box 220)
        - Vienna (Box 220)
        - Washington (Box 220)
    - BELLINI, Jacopo, ca. 1400-1470/71 (Box 220)
      - Drawings (Box 220)
      - Paintings (Box 220)
        - Brescia (Box 220)
        - Verona (Box 220)
        - Washington (Box 220)
    - BELLOTTO, Bernardo, 1721-1780 (Box 221)
    - BELTRAFFIO, Giovanni Antonio, 1467-1516 (Box 221)
    - BENEDETTO di Bindo (Box 221)
    - BENOZZO Gozzoli, ca. 1421-1497 (Box 221–222)
      - Florence (Box 222)
        - Medici Chapel (Box 222)
          - Journey of the Magi (Box 222)
            - Right Side: Lorenzo (Box 222)
            - Left Side: Riders with Cheetahs (Box 222)
            - Rear Wall: John Paleologus (Box 222)
          - Paradise (Box 222)
            - Right (Box 222)
            - Left (Box 222)
      - London (Box 222)
        - S. Francesco (Box 222)
      - Orvieto (Box 222)
      - Pisa (Box 222)
        - S. Gimignano (Box 222)
        - S. Agostino (Box 222)
      - Washington (Box 222)
    - BENEVENUTO di Giovanni di Meddel del Guasta, 1436-1518 (Box 222)
      - Siena (Box 222)
      - Washington (Box 222)
    - BERNARDINO di Mariotto, fl. 1496-1566 (Box 222)
    - BERNINI, Giovanni Lorenzo, 1598-1680 (Box 222)
      - Drawings (Box 222)
      - Paintings (Box 222)
    - BERTUCCI, Giovanni Batista (Box 222)
    - BESOZZO, Michelino Molinari da, fl. ca. 1390-1410 (Box 222)
    - BIAGIO d' Antonio da Firenze, fl. 1467-1504 (Box 222)
    - BIANCHI, Pietro, 1694-1740 (Box 222)
    - BIBIENA (Box 222)
    - BIROLLI, Renato, 1906- (Box 222)
    - BOCCACCINO, Boccaccio, 1467 to 1524-1525 (Box 222)
    - BOCCATI, Giovanni, b. ca.1420, fl. 1480 (Box 222)
    - BOCCIONI, Umberto, 1882-1916 (Box 222–223)
    - BOLTRAFFIO, Giovanni Antonio, 1467-1516 (Box 223)
    - BOMBELLI, Sebastiano, 1635-1716 (Box 223)
    - BONFIGLI, Benedetto (Box 223)
    - BONIFAZIO, Veronese, 1487-1553 (Box 223)
    - BONO, Michele di Taddeo (Gambono), fl. 1420-1462 (Box 223)
    - BONO da Ferrara, fl. 1442-1461 (Box 223)
    - BONISIGNORI, Francesco, 1455-1519 (Box 223)
    - BONZI, Pietro Paolo (Box 223)
    - BORDONE, Paris Paschalinus, 1500-1571 (Box 223)
      - Genoa (Box 223)
      - London (Box 223–224)
      - Milan (Box 224)
      - Rome (Box 224)
      - Venice (Box 224)
      - Vienna (Box 224)
      - Washington (Box 224)
    - BORGHINI, Vincenzo, fl. 1565 (Box 224)
    - BORGIANNI, Orazio, ca.1578-1616 (Box 224)
    - BORGOGNONE, Ambrogio di Stephano, 1455-1535 (Box 224)
    - BOTTICELLI, Sandro, 1444?-1510 (Box 224–226)
      - Drawings (Box 224–226)
        - Illustrations for Dante's Divine Comedy (Box 224–226)
      - Paintings (Box 224–226)
        - Berlin (Box 224–226)
          - Kaiser-Friedrich (Box 224–226)
        - Boston (Box 224–226)
        - Cambridge (Box 224–226)
        - Florence (Box 224–226)
          - Ognissanti (Box 224–226)
          - Palazzo Pitti (Box 224–226)
          - Uffizi (Box 224–226)
            - Annunciation (Box 224–226)
            - Adoration of the Magi (Box 224–226)
            - Birth of Venus (Box 224–226)
            - Calumny of Apelles (Box 224–226)
            - Coronation of the Virgin (Box 224–226)
            - Judith and Holofernes (Box 224–226)
            - Magnificent Madonna (Box 224–226)
            - Madonna of the Pomegranate (Box 224–226)
            - Pallas and the Centaur (Box 224–226)
            - Primavera (Box 224–226)
            - S. Barnabas Altarpiece (Box 224–226)
          - Frankfurt (Box 224–226)
          - London (Box 224–226)
            - National Gallery (Box 224–226)
          - Milan (Box 224–226)
          - New York (Box 224–226)
          - Paris (Box 224–226)
            - Louvre (Box 224–226)
          - Philadelphia (Box 224–226)
          - Rome (Box 224–226)
            - Vatican-Sistine Chapel (Box 224–226)
              - Moses and the Daughters of Jethro (Box 224–226)
          - Venice (Box 224–226)
          - Washington (Box 224–226)
    - BOTTICINI, Francesco, 1446 to 1497-1498 (Box 226)
    - BRAMANTE, Donato da Urbino, 1444-1514 (Box 226)
    - BRAMANTINO (Box 226)
    - BRANDI, Giacinto (Box 226)
    - BREA da Nizza Ludovico, 1443-1520? (Box 226)
    - BRESCIANINO (Box 226)
    - BRONZINO, Agnolo, 1503-1572 (Box 226–227)
      - Berlin (Box 227)
      - Florence (Box 227)
      - London (Box 227)